Did you cut this yourself today? Yes, that's right Where did all this meat go? At this rate, I don’t think I can pay you today There were bones, bones everywhere Aren’t you the sunbae here?
That’s right If you teach like this, who’s going to take responsibility? Oh no… Isn’t it the senior's job to manage the juniors properly? (Asa/ Rora/ BABYMONSTER) Asa
Do you think you can film Workdol while on a world tour? Washing dishes? Cleaning the grill? I'll do whatever needs to be done (Cheating) Don't look too closely (Just wait)
Do you not understand even if I write the lines? (Memory issue) It's okay (Take two) Asa Do you think you can film Workdol while on a world tour? Washing dishes? Cleaning the grill?
I'll do whatever needs to be done Don't let anyone else decide my worth My life is just getting started, and I'm going to live eating only the finest steak So, where am I working today?
At a steakhouse Think I can sneak a bite? I can probably take a bite, right? (Rich man's hotspot Wolfgang) (Steakhouse part-timer) I've heard this place is really expensive
(A place where the wealthy come to dine) They say a lot of rich folks visit this steakhouse So today, Asa unnie is treating me to steak Um, let me think about that for a second My bank account is
pretty much empty right now (Actually came here to make money) (3-00 PM - Heading to work) Since I'm a bit more experienced
(Workdol experienced worker's bluff) - Follow me - Because you're experienced But today, since many high-profile people are coming, let's maintain our dignity Right How's everyone doing?
How's everyone doing? (Dignity that raises doubts about her hometown) - In this kind of vibe - It's strange Hello Hello Welcome to our Wolfgang Steakhouse!
(Han Soomin) (3rd year) We're the best steakhouse in South Korea I've heard that many VIPs and business people come here often They host parties and events as well
(Q. Who was the prettiest?) Then, is there an artist who left the biggest impression on you? For me, it's BLACKPINK Uh Oh, wowww Amazing (Feeling that YG hype) (Stop) Before we get started,
let me just say a few things The kitchen can be a really dangerous place Knives can go flying around Whoa! And flames can suddenly flare up all over the place Whoa! So you need to get yourself in line
(Yes, sir) and start working with discipline (Nervously alert) - Yes, understood - Got it? (3:30 PM - Meat prep) You'll now follow me and work on the meat If you two don't do it right,
you're going to get scolded (Is this the start of strict discipline...?) We'll get in trouble...? How should I address you? (Strictly) Please call me Chef Soomin senpai Soomin senpai
Chef Soomin to you That's really, really cute (Disarmed) In Japan, they'd call him senpai Now, let's head into the aging room (Serious) It's kind of like a trade secret Oh wow A trade secret
(A rather feeble warning) - You can't tell anyone about this - Seriously, don't tell anyone (Entering) These are some seriously expensive cuts of meat Amazing That's a huge amount
We carefully select just 2% of American beef, (Only the finest, handpicked beef) and then dry-age it ourselves using our own expertise
(Q. How much is all this?) So, about how much are these meats worth? If you pack it all in, nearly a billion won? Whoa! A billion won (Time to snatch and run) Let's grab one
How many kilos is each one? Each one weighs 15 kilos Whoa On average, - they're about 13 to 15 kilos each - Wow, that's really heavy
(Conspiring openly) We could just carry it together when we head out (Time to move the meat) Now we have to take this meat outside (Trying to act tough) Whoa, Asa, there's no way you can lift this
(Offended) I've been working out lately Asa works out (This is tough) Oh, wait a second (The dream of embezzlement is gone) Let’s just share one between us, this isn’t going to work Let’s start with
(Performance) the trimming step first Don’t act like an idol Keep it classy (Flirting confiscation for a moment) Okay Alright, let’s try trimming this
(The process of removing unnecessary parts to improve meat quality) You cut away all the inedible bits Alright, let me show you first, and then you can try it yourself Okay
(Sneak peek) You have to watch closely, Asa I'm watching carefully Don't mess up the meat, okay? We'll get complaints if you do They say this is tenderloin Doesn't that make you feel tender?
(Seriously...) Okay, always be careful with knives (Right up to it) Watch your fingers (Trimming the meat 1. Removing the fat layer) Carefully trim away the fat
(2. Remove any unnecessary parts) Trim off all the excess meat like this (3. Trimming) - Make it look nice - Now it's just pure tenderloin left If you slip with the knife,
you'll lose ten or twenty thousand won just like that Whoa! Have you ever gotten in trouble for slicing something wrong? Oh, plenty of times Get over to the freezer It was kind of like that vibe
(Turns out, it was the room of truth..?) Luckily, I wasn't actually hit (Straight into action) Let's have you two give it a try I used to be a bit of a kid chef, you know Oh
(Experienced chef) - That's right, you were a kids' chef - I can trust you in the kitchen What about Asa? I'm pretty good at cooking I even make galbijjim (For real?) (Professional-level air slicing)
You're not able to use a knife at all? (How did you even make galbijjim?) Hold on a second (Extra lesson) Let me show you one more time (Meanwhile, straight back to chopping) Just follow the bone down
(Is this what experience looks like?) Aren't I doing pretty well? Yeah, you're doing great (Slicing through with ease) - I think you should get hired here - You're a real catch, you know?
(Finished 5 pieces in no time) I think it's best to stop here for now Hold on a second Whoa, is this right? (Couldn't even finish one piece here) (In the middle of a battle) What are you doing?
Asa, what are you thinking about right now? Huh? I don't think we should talk to Asa right now (Slide) I'm super focused right now No way No way? We're doomed (So doomed) It's doomed
I told you, don't talk to me Mmm-hmm We need to set the bone Ah (Refocusing) Uh She messed it up (Still cutting into the money) Chef, we've got 20,000 won deducted here It's time to summon the fridge
(To the room of truth) Follow me to the freezer Oh no unnie, if you're dragged away later, I'm not responsible Looks like I'm getting dragged away It's not bad? Shall we try a bit more here?
What else should we do? She needs to learn again Can you eat this? - No - No, you can't - You can't eat it - So what do we do? Eliminate Asa We can't let Asa get eliminated (Be careful)
What if Asa gets eliminated? Now, you'll also get to meet your sunbaes in the second floor kitchen We're in trouble I think we're really going to get scolded then (Prepare to get wrecked)
(4:30 PM - Grilling Training) - Hello - I'm a new recruit Before we start grilling this, let's get our head chef Our big boss (Yikes) Whoa Let's have the chief inspect this first
Get ready to be scolded What are you saying? You should get ready (Head chef appears) Hello (A step back) How do you do Whoa Did you cut this yourself today? Yes, that's right
Would you mind if I check it over? Please do (Trimming evaluation begins) With eagle eyes (Nervous...) (Tilts head) Where did all this meat go? (The culprit) At this rate,
I don’t think I can pay you today Uh... No way (It’s the bones) There were bones, bones everywhere Aren’t you the sunbae here? That’s right If you teach like this, who’s going to take responsibility?
(Nervous/ Super nervous) Oh, no (Getting a harsh scolding) Isn’t it the senior's job to manage the juniors properly? Yes, sir How are we going to take responsibility for this? (Awkward silence) Boss
We'll do the dishes Next time, we'll invite you to our concert (Grin) Oh, really? (In a flash) Alright, I'll take responsibility for this (Speechless) Thank you (Thanks for the smooth deal)
Now, let's get started grilling the meat What should we do first? Season it Right (Steak cooking) (1. Salt it well) You need to sprinkle salt evenly from the shaker Let it go, let it go
- That's right, evenly - Evenly, evenly, evenly, evenly (2. Put it in the broiler) We'll lift it using tongs You can hear the sound, right? (Sizzling) It's sizzling right now Be careful, Asa
Here I come Asa is coming You can handle it, Asa (Landing with a splash) Well done So here, we'll sear the top and bottom One, two, three, sear (Steak tribute performance) Sear
Okay, now watch as I take it off Ooh, wow (Perfectly cooked) - That looks absolutely delicious - Doesn't it look amazing? (Under surveillance) Could you flip it over once?
The top side is just about done now So when you get together with your friends, who grills the meat? That's just part of the job hazard I end up grilling every time
- Oh - If my friends grill it, it tastes so bad I can't eat it Whoa (Rapid-fire questions) Are you team beef, or team pork? Me Since I also like to drink, (Totally absorbed) I usually have
soju and beer with pork (What are you guys doing?) - Yeah, right - Wow, seriously (Startled) (End of banter) We need to do this quickly (Picking up) Yaaah! So scary, so scary
Now we're going to do a second round of trimming Whoa (Second trimming) (T-bone cutting) Keep the knife as close to the bone as possible Stay close
(Tenderloin cutting) Just divide the tenderloin into three equal pieces The key here is uniformity, right? (Sirloin cutting) I'll do my best Yes, just cut them all the same
(Starting to micromanage) Exactly the same, they all have to be identical Are you sure about that? (Zap) Did you feel that? (Instant Cowering Ending)
(5:30 PM - Briefing) Let’s have a quick meeting before dinner service (Kang Beomjoon) (General Manager) We have a lot of dinner reservations today (Group precision on point) We have 34 parties
(Sneaky glance) and 118 guests booked Asa, let's straighten our backs too Tuck in your stomach (Important note) And when we do the sizzling, it's really hot Please be careful to avoid any accidents
I have a question What's sizzling? This is when we bring out a dry-aged steak on a huge plate. It's extremely hot (Warning: extremely hot) - Please be careful - Understood
(Q. Challenges of floor serving?) What would you say is the hardest part about working on the floor? For younger staff, it's often tough to make eye contact and communicate directly with customers
Yeah, that's true But the more challenging it feels, the more you need to make eye contact (Staring) That's how you really connect with the customers Is it okay for her to be this forward?
- That startled me - Are we doing all right? Are you comfortable? Is there anything you need? What can we get for you? (Sweating) Would you like some water? You're overbearing Okay
I'll make sure you're comfortable and warm (Already worried) Thank you so much (Getting to work) Customers have just arrived, so I'll go take their orders with you (Park Nayei) (5 months) Alright
Come this way Do you ever get any complaints? (Worried) It really depends on how you handle it Oh wow, you really have to be on top of your game (Person to watch out for) Excuse me Yes
For today’s main, we’ll be serving a porterhouse steak How would you like your steak cooked? Do you have a recommendation? Medium rare to medium (Gathering answers) Medium rare
We also tend to recommend medium rare (Playful) (Better run before I mess up) I'll make sure everything's perfect for you (Looking confused) So, where are we headed now? Please come this way
(Fresh bread served right away) - Trust me, I'm really good at this - Watch closely Oh, wow (Looks like this could take all day...) This is really hard to cut It just won't cut properly
Maybe if I try a little more... (GG) Oh, Rora Oh my She only managed to cut two pieces Rora, please help me out (Snips right through) Oh my See? Oh my (Retry) (My whole body is shaking)
What do you think? Where do you think someone like that would fit in? A bar? Maybe serving or in the kitchen? If she keeps working hard If she keeps working hard When does it get cut?
(It's faster to cut this one) Come on, come on (Finally escaped) Hello, everyone Here is your bread appetizer to start the meal Now, please tell us about the bread Baguette Baguette and (Malfunction)
(Changing the subject) Do you come here often? Or is this your first time visiting? (Here for their anniversary) We had something to celebrate Could you tell us how you two met?
(Excited anticipation) Us? We met at a book club (So wholesome…) But we actually got close over drinks (A sudden twist) This story is moving fast (Now I'm curious) Do you have a boyfriend? No, I don't
Oh my gosh (Such a wild turn) You can't ask us questions like that, that's dangerous Now, our VIP client is waiting for us outside
(VIP suite escort) - We'll personally take them to their room - Understood Hang on a second (Can we go now...?) - Okay, let's go - Let's go Hello Hello Welcome (Surprised by Babymonster) Wow Japanese?
We're Japanese Ah (Feeling more confident in her native language) Let me show you to your room Please come this way (Entering the private room) Since my Japanese isn't very good,
I'll need your help with interpreting (Becomes the interpreter) Let's go Alright The food for your meal is Everyone, hi (Error) Just a moment (Native language buffering)
How would you like your steak cooked? (Second challenge) Steak Medium rare It's medium rare (What is this?) Do you speak Korean? Hi A little bit (Turns out they're foreign students, lol)
(Why use an interpreter?) What? Can you speak Korean? (Serving the steak right away) Now, let's go get our main steak When we make a request to the kitchen, we say, "Is a via possible for table 31?"
What's a via? It means, "Let's go" Let's go (Loudly) Can we get a via at table 31? Via Via (This is such a rush...!) (Waiting) Do you get a lot of troublesome customers here?
Back when I used to work here, I was cleaning up tables and someone threw their trash right at me like this (Getting caught up in drama while working hard) - That time, I felt - A bit hurt
That was just plain rude (Ready to go full battle mode) (The steak is ready) Main course coming through (Security mode) Main course coming through - Careful, - Everyone, be careful
Wow, that steak looks amazing Oh, that looks delicious Steak coming through Precious Coming through, here comes your dish Watch your step (It looks seriously hot) - It's really hot - It's really hot
It's really hot, twice Please be careful, it's hot (Lands safely) I'll bring it to the side (Most skilled so far today) This is stir-fried kimchi Mashed potatoes Yoon Jaehyuk sunbae? Huge success
(Senior from the same agency TREASURE’s Jaehyuk spotted) (Can’t let them win) We’ve got to show off as MONSTIEZ too Show off, show off (The girls we want to steal) Steal them
We go up like whoa, we’re the villains, villains Up high for me, baby (Watching the new song live) This is how we do it, we go oh (Totally knocked over)
(They keep serving steaks) - Here comes the main dish - Main dish coming up Main dish coming up Watch out, everyone Watch your step Alright, it's hot, hot, so hot! So hot, so hot! Hurry, hurry, hurry!
Quick, before it cools down! Excuse me. I'll bring your steak right out (Steak under maximum protection) Your steak has arrived (Serving the next table) Careful, it's hot
(Moving with exaggerated caution) Please be careful, please be careful Excuse me Please be careful, just a moment It's hot, so watch out
(Appeal) This is the steak we've carefully prepared and cut for you, so you can enjoy it with tender heart (Awkward silence as the meat gets cold) - Thank you - Enjoy your meal
(Greeting) Is everything going well with your meal? Yes. (Greeting 22) Are you enjoying your meal? Oh, yes It's absolutely delicious May I ask what your relationship is? We're a couple Wow!
We're getting married next week Oh my (Found my favorite spot) (Q. Girlfriend's best features) Three attractive features of your girlfriend (Expectations) First,
being held makes me feel incredibly at ease (Fully immersed) Aww Second She's just so beautiful (Beauty acknowledged) - Third - Third Makes money way too well Oh wow, that's the important part
(Say no more) That's why they're getting married (8:00 PM - Off work) It's over (Back in the freezer warehouse) Thank you for your hard work Thank you It's done (Shivering) Ha ha (Nom)
Ten thousand, twenty thousand, thirty thousand won Three, four Sixty-two thousand five hundred won (Steakhouse payout Total: 62,500 won) How many hours? Five hours
- So that’s ten thousand won per hour - Whoa So we’re actually getting a bit more than ten thousand won Whoa You’re quick at calculating this kind of thing, right? (Shiver) Whoa Give me your hand
Okay, okay, okay Out of five points Hmm Hmm... 3.5 points Oh, oh wow, wait a second (Steakhouse job satisfaction Fun meeting customers 5.0 That feeling
Strict atmosphere 3.0 Freezer smell 3.0) when you get to congratulate customers, see couples, feel proud That was fun Yeah I think that's the kind of happiness that keeps me going
And then out in the hall, it gets pretty intense Boss The captains are so Chef - It was a bit scary - Yeah, understandable Mhm Today was my first Workdol,
and I had such a great time because it left such a strong impression My rating is also 3.5 stars, just like Asa unnie
(Steakhouse work satisfaction Kitchen is a bit scary 3.0 Honestly, the kitchen is really scary True Introvert issue 3.0 Fun meeting customers 5.0) So I think it might tough for introverted people
(Today’s ending pose?) Since we’re at a fancy restaurant, let’s sing “Rich Man” once, so we can become rich ourselves someday I am a Rich Man (Chilling concert in the freezer warehouse)
I am a Rich Man But our new song is coming out soon (Please check out “We Go Up” too!) (Q. Ever been confessed with a letter?) Asa, have you ever gotten a love letter? Oh, plenty of times
Actually, I have a story about that (A little trip down memory lane) It was the last day of school, and I found a confession letter inside my shoe Stop it Are you even listening to my story?
(Bored) Oh, I’ve heard that so many times But I saw that in Korea, so I never actually met him (Summary) So the shoes with the letter inside came straight to Korea just like that True
I was just dancing, and suddenly, huh? Is there something in my shoe? I took it out to look, and there was (A letter) a letter inside So (That's enough now)